this is going to be a 60 second product
review video this is a Tarmac Works
Toyota Supra GT part of the jgtc 1995
series and part of their latest tooling
that they've done this is actually a
special edition model that was released
overseas during a special event tarback
Works making some awesome Livery type
cars this one is a metal diecast cool
Livery it's got a really nice base
rocking those awesome yellow headlights
love that love the Livery love all the
spawn ship decals this is a car that
does exist in real life the wheel setup
the polished lip the tires Tire stickers
all there rear you can see the
three-piece wing and you can also see
the widen body as well typically about
the 20-ish to 22 range and if you're a
fan of the Toyota Supra this is one to
for sure check out if you want to see
more content like this be sure to
subscribe and I'll see you in the next
video